steelcase.com 2006-06-16

# Steelcase - Privacy Policy - Privacy Policy

| 

Introduction  
Welcome to Steelcase.com (which includes Leap.Steelcase.com and 360Steelcase.com) (the "Site"). This Site is owned by Steelcase Inc. This Privacy Policy is designed to tell you how this Site collects, uses, and discloses the information you provide via this Site. **By using this Site, you acknowledge that you have reviewed, and agree to, the terms of this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use, do not use this Site.**

Scope of Privacy Policy / Links  
This Privacy Policy applies only to this Site. Although this Site may provide you with links to other websites, including those of our business partners and/or service providers, those websites are not covered by this Privacy Policy. Likewise, although this Site may provide links to websites that are owned or operated by us or our affiliates, this Privacy Policy does not apply to such websites. We strongly encourage you to read the privacy policy of every website you visit, including those websites to which this Site provides links. Whenever you link to any other website from this Site, you are solely responsible for any interactions you may have with that website. Links from this Site to other websites will typically open in a separate browser window while the browser window for this Site remains open in the background.

This Site provides a link to a third party web-site that allows you to enroll for electronic delivery of our proxy statement, annual report, and related materials as an alternative to receiving such materials by mail. This third-party website gathers certain personally identifiable information (e.g., your Social Security Number and email address) to process your enrollment. Even though this third-party website may be branded with the Steelcase logo, it is operated by Investor Communication Services ("ICS") and any information you submit through that website is subject to the terms of ICS's website privacy policy, which is available at www.icsdelivery.com. Our Privacy Policy does not apply to the ICS website.

Who Should Use this Site  
This Site is not intended for use by children under the age of 13, and we will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from such individuals.

Active Information Collection  
At various points on this Site, you might choose to actively provide certain kinds of information, including personally identifiable information, such as full name, address, phone number, e-mail address, etc. The Site typically will indicate which information is required and which information is optional at the information collection point in question. In any case, by submitting information via an active information collection point at this Site, you specifically consent to the collection, use, and dissemination of such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Active information collection points at this Site may include:

Email Reply Mechanisms  
This Site may provide you with one or more e-mail reply mechanisms through which you may submit questions or comments. Information you provide via such e-mail reply mechanisms is typically all optional. We may use the information you provide in your e-mail to respond to your inquiry, and we reserve the right to retain whatever information you submit in your e-mail, including your name, e-mail address, and any comments or other information that you send via the e-mail reply mechanism.

Question, Comment, and Feedback Forms  
This Site may post a form for you to use in submitting questions, comments, and other feedback about us, our affiliates, this Site, our or our affiliates' products and services, and other topics. We use such feedback information to improve this Site, and our or our affiliates' products and services as well as for marketing and research purposes. Most information you provide in such forms is optional, but you will need to provide at least some personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, e-mail address, and phone number, so that we may respond to your inquiry.

Product Information, and Catalog Request Forms  
This Site may include a form that you can use to request information about us, our affiliates, or our or our affiliates' products and services, or to request catalogs or brochures. In addition to asking you to identify the specific information or materials in which you are interested, these forms may request, among other things, your name, address, and e-mail address, so that we may send you the information or materials you request. These forms may also request certain demographic information about you to help us better understand your interests and needs.

Software Download Form  
This Site may include a form that you must complete before receiving a software download from the Site. This form may request, among other things, your name, address, and e-mail address. The form also requests certain information about the computer systems you are using. We use this information to keep track of software downloads and to learn more about what computer systems and configurations visitors to the Site use. We also may use this information to send you updated versions of the software as they become available and to notify you of problems with the software.

Surveys and Evaluations  
The Site may ask you to complete optional surveys and evaluations about us, our affiliates, this Site, our or our affiliates' products and services, and other topics. These surveys and evaluations might request personally identifiable information, such as your name and e-mail address, so that we can follow up with you. Typically, we use such surveys and evaluations to better understand our customers and their preferences.

Registration Forms  
Because access to portions of this Site is restricted to authorized users, you may be required to complete a registration form. This form may ask you for a variety of information that will help us to identify you and contact you, such as your name, business address, office e-mail address, office phone number, and your relationship to us. Where you could be using the Site to place orders, we will also ask you for billing and shipping information. Registration information will be associated with your username and password, without which you will not be able to access the restricted portions of the Site.

Employment Applications  
This Site provides a link to a third-party website, HotJobs.com, which allows you to search our available jobs and submit an online employment application. If you submit an online employment application, you will be disclosing any personally identifiable information you have included in your application to HotJobs.com, which in turn shares that information with us. Even though the online employment application has the Steelcase logo, you should be aware that HotJobs.com will use any information you submit via the online employment application in accordance with your registration instructions and its privacy policy, which is available at the HotJobs.com website. Please be sure that you have reviewed, and agree to, the terms of the HotJobs.com privacy policy before you submit an online employment application. If you do not agree to those terms, do not submit an online employment application.

The online employment application requests certain types of personally identifiable information, including your name, address, and e-mail address, as well as your previous work experience and salary expectations. We may use and disseminate this information internally and among our affiliates as necessary to consider your application and to contact you regarding our decision. We may also use this information from time to time to inform you of other employment opportunities and related information that may be of interest to you. We do not use or disclose this information other than for the purposes described here. Please contact us as specified in the "Let's Talk" section if you no longer wish to receive such information from us or our affiliates or be considered for employment opportunities with us or our affiliates. If you have any questions regarding HotJobs.com's use of information you submit in an online employment application and your ability to update or delete such information, please consult the HotJobs.com website.

To comply with various government recordkeeping requirements, the application may also ask you to provide certain other optional categories of information about yourself. Providing or not providing such information will not adversely affect your employment prospects, and such information will not become part of your employment application or our or our affiliates' employment files.

E-Mail Newsletters, Alerts, or Reminders  
The Site may ask you to provide your e-mail address so that you can receive e-mail newsletters, alerts, or reminders about us, our affiliates, our Site, our or our affiliates' products and services, and other topics of interest. If you no longer wish to receive such e-mails, please follow the "unsubscribe" instructions included in such e-mails or contact us as described below.

Purchasing/Order Processing Information  
This Site allows you to purchase our products and services online. As a result, the Site gathers certain personally identifiable information (e.g., your name and address) and payment information (e.g., your credit card number) to process your order. Specifically, we may: (i) use and disclose the information you provide as necessary to process and ship your order (e.g., by disclosing your name and address to fulfillment houses and delivery services such as UPS or Federal Express, (ii) use the personally identifiable information you provide to notify you about the status of your order, (iii) retain this information to create an account for later use (so that you do not need to re-enter the information for each subsequent order); (iv) group your de-identified information with that of other Site users to provide information to us about group purchasing and preferences; and (v) share this information (other than payment information) with our affiliates, business partners, and dealers.

Leasing Credit Application  
The Site may post an online credit application for businesses interested in leasing our products. Among other things, this application asks for your business's name, address, and phone number, the nature of the business, certain insurance information, background and credit information about the officers and owners of your business. Steelcase Financial Services uses the information you provide to evaluate, and contact you regarding, your credit application. Steelcase Financial Services does not share this information with any third party without your express permission except as necessary to review your credit application or to perform related tasks.

My Steelcase  
The "My Steelcase" area of the Site allows you to establish a personalized account to organize contact information, create folders for storing your favorite pages of the Site, and to receive news about our company, our affiliates, and our and our affiliates' products and services. My Steelcase also allows you to e-mail pages of the Site to others. To register for My Steelcase, you must provide some personally identifiable information, including your name and e-mail address. You may also choose to provide optional information, including your address and phone number. We use the information you submit on the My Steelcase registration form to automatically fill out other online forms on the Site that you want to submit and to help maintain your My Steelcase account. When you wish to send an e-mail to someone through My Steelcase, we use the recipient's e-mail address only to send the requested e-mail and for no other purpose.

Other Functions  
This Site may offer tests, quizzes, search functions, calculators, or conversion tools that help you learn more about various topics. We use the information you input while using these functions to provide you with immediate feedback.

Passive Information Collection  
This Site uses various technologies to passively collect information from you while you are visiting (that is, you do not actively provide this information). Such technologies allow the Site to collect a range of nonpersonally identifiable information, including your Internet Protocol (IP) address (a unique identifier automatically assigned to your computer when logging onto the Internet), the type of Web browser and operating system you use, the date and time you visit the Site, the specific pages you visit on the Site, and the address of the website you visited before coming to this Site. We typically use such passively collected information for a variety of purposes, such as to administer the Site, customize the Site to your preferences, and compile aggregated statistics for marketing and research purposes. We reserve the unrestricted right to use this passively collected, nonpersonally identifiable information, including, but not limited to, selling, leasing, permitting access to, or otherwise transferring it to our affiliates, business partners, advertisers, dealers, and other third parties.

Two types of passive information collection technologies deserve special mention:

Cookies  
"Cookies" are small text files that store information about your interactions with a particular website, either temporarily (known as a "temporary" or "session" cookie, and deleted once you close your browser window) or more permanently on the hard drive of your computer (known as a "permanent" or "persistent cookie"). Cookies can make it easier to use a website by allowing servers to access certain information quickly:

  * **Session cookies** can be used to help a user's browser navigate a website more smoothly and may show up if the user comes from a website with which the subsequent website has some relationship (e.g., a website of an affiliated company) and can give helpful information.
  * **Persistent cookies** can be used to customize a website for a user, such as by storing passwords, preferences, and registration and account information so that users do not have to reenter them each time they visit a website.

This Site uses both session/temporary cookies and persistent/permanent cookies to store information that allows us to offer you better customer service and to navigate through the Site with ease. To make the Site easier to use, we combine information collected via cookies with personally identifiable information. Note that if you configure your browser to reject cookies, you might not be able to access important functions or areas of the Site or enjoy certain conveniences at this Site.

Web Beacons  
"Web beacons" (also known as single-pixel GIFs, clear GIFs, invisible GIFs, and 1-by-1 GIFs) are Internet tags that are smaller than cookies and may tell the website server nonpersonally identifiable information such as the IP address and browser type related to the user's computer. This Site does not use "Web beacons."

Other Uses and Disclosures of Information  
As indicated above, we use information we collect from you via this Site for a variety of purposes. Unless otherwise provided above, we may also use personally and nonpersonally identifiable information you submit via this Site in the following ways:

  * to tell you about new products and services or other information we think may be of interest to you. If you do not wish to receive such notifications or updates, please contact us at **[DOTCOM@Steelcase.com](mailto:DOTCOM@Steelcase.com)** or **DOTCOM, PO Box 1967, CD-4S-14, Grand Rapids, MI 49501-1967** and specify which notifications or updates you do not wish to receive;
  * to conduct internal marketing and research; and
  * to improve the content of the Site.

From time to time, our service providers may have access to information you submit via the Site to provide operational or other support services for the Site (e.g., Web hosting or database services). We have put in place agreements with such service providers to protect against unauthorized uses or disclosures of such information.

Except as otherwise provided in the "Active Information Collection" section above, we also reserve the right to sell, lease, provide access, or otherwise transfer personally identifiable information you submit via this Site to our business partners (including e-mail delivery services and content providers), affiliates, and dealers for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy.

**Notwithstanding anything to the contrary in this Privacy Policy or elsewhere on this Site, we reserve the right to share or transfer any information you submit via this Site to another person or company in connection with the sale, assignment, or other transfer of the business of this Site and/or Steelcase Inc.; to respond to law enforcement requests; or where required by applicable law, statute, regulation, ordinance, subpoena, or court order. By submitting personally identifiable information via this Site, you consent to such disclosures in accordance with this Privacy Policy.**

Information Access  
We take reasonable measures to ensure that personally identifiable information that we collect from you via this Site is accurate, current, complete, and reliable for its intended uses. If you wish to update or otherwise correct personally identifiable information you have provided to us, please resubmit the applicable form on the Site with the updated information or contact us as described in the "Ask Us" section. If you have questions related to employment, use the "Let's Talk" email response form.

We will make reasonable efforts to respond to your inquiry, but we may require follow-up or contact information to allow us to verify that you are the person authorized to view the information you are requesting. We may, in our discretion, refuse to allow you access to certain information if, in our view, to provide such access would jeopardize another person's privacy; would violate any applicable federal, state, or foreign law, regulation, or directive; or would unreasonably burden this Site.

Data Security  
Although we take steps to protect personally identifiable information you provide via this Site from loss, misuse, or unauthorized alteration, no system is 100% secure or error-free. Therefore, we do not, and cannot, guarantee the security or accuracy of the information we collect via this Site, and you acknowledge that you are assuming the risk in transmitting any information to us.

We use the SSL (Secure Socket Layer) industry standard for encrypting all ordering data, including credit card transactions. SSL provides one of the highest levels of security available today for web-based sales, using encryption technologies developed by Verisign, Inc., and RSA Data Security, Inc. We also use CyberSource to process online credit card transactions. CyberSource is a leading developer and provider of enterprise eCommerce transaction services, and a pioneer in the area of Internet fraud detection. You should be aware that other transmissions submitted via this Site (e.g., forms, e-mails, etc.) are not protected by the same security measures we use for ordering data. As a result, you should be particularly careful in deciding what information you wish to send to us.

**It is your responsibility to safeguard any usernames and passwords you use to access portions of this Site and to notify us if you ever suspect that these usernames or passwords have been compromised. You acknowledge that you are solely responsible for any unauthorized use of this Site conducted via your username or password.**

Ask Us / Enforcement of this Privacy Policy  
If at any time you have questions, comments, or concerns about this Privacy Policy, or the information practices of this Site, please contact us in one of the following ways:

E-Mail:
    **Use theAsk Us form provided on this Site**
Mail:
    **DotCom  
PO Box 1967  
CD-4S-14  
Grand Rapids, MI 49501**
Phone:
    **1-800-333-9939**

We will take reasonable steps to respond to your inquiry and remedy any problems you may bring to our attention.

Changes to this Privacy Policy  
If this Privacy Policy changes, the revised Policy will be posted here and the date of the newest version will be posted below. Please check back frequently, especially before you submit any personally identifiable information at this Site, to see if the Privacy Policy has changed.

This Privacy Policy was last revised on March 15, 2002.
